Guide to the Brooklyn playbills and programs collection BCMS.0041
Brooklyn Collection
Brooklyn playbills and programs collection
1875-2017
1880-1950
Brooklyn Collection
BCMS.0041
2.25 Linear Feet in 3 boxes
This collection consists of hundreds of playbills and programs for events that either took place in Brooklyn or, in some cases, are thematically related to Brooklyn.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged in series alphabetically by venue name. Items are listed chronologically within each series.
Conditions Governing Access
Open to researchers without restriction.
Related Materials
Highlights from the Brooklyn Theater Playbills and Programs Collection: 15 digitized items from this collection, all from Brooklyn theaters.
Brooklyn Newsstand: This database includes Brooklyn periodicals that covered and advertised local performing arts events that are found in this collection.
Theater Playbills and Programs at the Library of Congress
Cambridge Guide to American Theatre. Cambridge, UK: Cambridge University Press, 1996.
Collection Highlights
•A 1913 program for "The Heart and the Hand," a joint address by Helen Keller and her teacher, Mrs. John Macy (also known as Anne Sullivan) at the Brooklyn Academy of Music.
•The earliest film program in the collection is dated July 24, 1915, for D. W. Griffith's Birth of a Nation at the Brighton Beach Music Hall.
•Well-known and critically regarded stage actors, such as Sarah Bernhardt in "Fedora" at the Brooklyn Theatre on Fulton Street. There are also programs from multiple theaters for both plays and films starring the famous Barrymores: John, Ethel, and Lionel.
•There are numerous playbills featuring entertainment that includes famous Vaudevillians such as W.C. Fields, Pat Rooney, Stan Laurel, Ethel Merman, Marie Dressler, Jack Norworth and Nora Bayes (later to be known as Nora Bayes Norworth), Eddie Foy, Marie Cahill, Lillian Russell, Will Rogers, Stuart Robson and William Crane, and others. Vaudeville began to decline in popularity after the rise of radio and sound films, but many of these stage stars later went on to achieve success in motion pictures and their names can also be found in movie programs within the collection.
•Two playbills for Minsky's Burlesque, featuring a raucous and bawdy style of entertainment considered obscene at the time. The Minsky Brothers were the leading entrepreneurs of burlesque; at the height of their success they had six theaters in New York City.
•Playbill for "The Two Orphans" performed at the Brooklyn Theatre on Washington and Johnson Streets on December 5, 1876 – the night of the disastrous fire that killed nearly 300 people. The play and the fire were both covered extensively in the Brooklyn Daily Eagle.
•At least one program in Yiddish and English ( The Red Soldier at the Brighton Theatre), and four in German and English (Lessing Quartett at Saengerbund Hall, Duty is Duty [2 copies] and Heart's Blood at the Hansa Theatre).
Historical note
In the days before television, theaters were an important place for entertainment, news, and social life, and hosted a range of performance genres. At one point, there were over 200 theaters in Brooklyn. Frequented by every class of Brooklynite, they enjoyed mass popularity. From the late 1880s until the 1940s, the period covered by the bulk of these materials, the performing arts thrived in Brooklyn and were available to Brooklyn residents right at their doorsteps.
Some theaters would provide more than one kind of entertainment; for instance, a theater might present a dramatic play and then at other times host vaudeville acts and variety shows. Movie theaters, particularly near the birth of the film medium, would often double as both movie and stage theaters, with film screenings often including vaudeville acts and news reels shown before, during, and after the feature presentation.
The playbills in this collection paint a vivid picture of the varieties of entertainment and cultural life available to Brooklyn residents across several decades. At the same time, they offer insights into prevailing attitudes and social preoccupations along with documenting changing tastes. At the Amphion Theatre, for example, a March 1900 playbill announces its current offering as The Carpet-Bagger, a "political romantic comedy in four acts" set in Mississippi. Adapted from the 1893 novel by Opie Read, a Tennessee-born writer and humorist, the piece draws heavily on broadly sketched, homespun characters that came to embody the Reconstruction-era South around the turn of the century. In contrast, a New Montauk Theatre playbill from just seven years later features considerably more sophisticated fare: a dramatic adaptation of Tolstoy's Anna Karenina and The Road to Yesterday, a lighthearted fantasy in which two unhappily married couples travel back to their previous lives in Elizabethan England. Both plays were presented by the Shubert Brothers, theater owners and managers who helped define the business of American theater in the 20th century.
The playbills also often include extensive advertising, sometimes accompanied by columns about current fashions, beauty hints, and automobiles. This illustrates the central role played by theaters in Brooklyn's daily life and commerce.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains materials representing over a century of events from over 100 different venues. The highest concentration is in the years 1890 to 1909, with over 400 items from that time period. Many of the items in the collection are in delicate condition and must be handled with care.
The types of events represented in this collection include motion pictures, musical concerts, high school commencement exercises, lectures, photoplays, vaudeville (which often included magic segments, song-and-dance acts, acrobatics, comic routines, short films, news reports, and animal acts), and burlesque, as well as the more traditional offerings such as plays and operas. There are also a few rare instances of postcards and stock photography. Theatrical genres represented include morality plays, musical comedies, drama, comedy, farce, satire, tragedy, romantic comedy, operas, and pantomime.
Numerous playbills confirm the range of programming that took place within a single venue. A Brighton Beach Music Hall playbill from the World War I period is typical of many in the collection. The theater's offerings include a screening of D.W. Griffith's Birth of a Nation; musical selections from Victor Herbert's The Tattooed Man; a performance of George M. Cohan's one-act musical farce The Governor's Son; and variety acts by magicians, street musicians, comedians, and acrobats. Elsewhere in the collection are unique items from a theater specializing in German cinema and printed programs with diagrams of theaters that no longer exist.
Advertisements occupy considerable space in many of the playbills. Most are from local businesses, especially ones located near the theaters. Fulton Street establishments, including ones promoted in our Fulton Street Trade Card Collection, are publicized as well.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
This is a composite collection compiled from multiple sources, primarily purchases. More items will continue to be added.
Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.); Concert programs; Concerts; Music-halls (Variety-theaters, cabarets, etc.); Theater; Theater programs; Theaters; Brooklyn Academy of Music
- Academy
  - [Photographic postcard of Ormi Hawley, Lubin Player], Undated (Box 1)
    General
    Advertising postcard with a photograph on the recto and information about the theatre on the verso.
- Alba
  - The Green Pastures, September 11, 1946 (Box 1)
    "The Green Pastures" a fable by Marc Connelly, September 11-14 [1936], plus Joe E. Brown in "Earthworm Tractors" (Program); "Crash Donovan" with Jack Holt, September 15-17 [1936], also "20,000 Years in Sing-Sing" with Spencer Tracy (Program).
- Albee
  - Vaudeville show, Pasquali Bros., Ryan and Ryan, January 25, 1925 (Box 1)
    "Topics Of The Day" produced by Timely Films, Inc., "Three Unusual Men" by Pasquali Bros.; "Song-Steps and Such" by Ryan and Ryan; "In a Pest House" by Roger Imhof, Marcelle Coreene and Co.; comedian Larry Semon; singer Nora Bayes; and more.
  - Vaudeville show, organ recital, orchestra, short films, acrobatics and comedy skits, May 11, 1925 (Box 1)
    Organ Recital played by Lee Woodbury; E.F. Albee Theatre Orchestra conducted by Andrew Byrne, Jr.; "Topics Of The Day" produced by Timely Films, Inc.; comedy skits; Aesop's Film Fables "Darkest Africa"; singers, and acrobatics.
  - Lovin' the Ladies, April 12, 1930 (Box 1)
    "Lovin' The Ladies" a motion picture with Richard Dix, Lois Wilson and Rita La Roy, from the Play by Wm. LeBaron, directed by Melville Brown, with the E.F. Albee R-K-Olian Ensemble, conducted by Salvatore Dell-Isola. Also featuring vaudeville acts.
- Alhambra
  - Three Wise Fools, March 31, 1924 (Box 1)
    The Alhambra Players present "3 Wise Fools," a play by Austin Strong. Staged by Cecil Owen. With Anne Bronaugh, John Warner, Frank Harrington. Technical Director, S. K. Fried.
  - Camille, April 7, 1924 (Box 1)
    The Alhambra Players present "Camille," a dramatic love story in Five Acts, by Alexander Dumas. With Anne Bronaugh, John Warner, Frank Harrington, Staged by Cecil Owen. Technical Director, S. K. Fried.
  - So This Is London [3 copies], September 29, 1924 (Box 1)
    The Alhambra Players present "So This Is London" A play in three acts by Arthur Goodrich, staged by Cecil Owen, with Henry Mortimer, Helen Gilmore, Frank Harrington, Anne Bronaugh, et al.
  - Smilin' Through, October 6, 1924 (Box 1)
    The Alhambra Players present "Smilin' Through" A play in a Prologue and Three Acts by Allan Langdon Martin, staged by Cecil Owen, with Mabel Montgomery, Helen Gilmore, Frank Harrington, Anne Bronaugh, et al. Associate Director, John Dugan.
  - Just Married, October 13, 1924 (Box 1)
    The Alhambra Players present "Just Married" A Comedy in Four Acts by Anne Nichols and Adelaide Matthews, staged by Cecil Owen, with Frank Mandel, Helen Gilmore, Frank Harrington, Anne Bronaugh, et al. Associate Director, John Dugan.
  - Secrets, November 10, 1924 (Box 1)
    The Alhambra Players present "Secrets" A Play in a Prologue, Three Acts and an Epilogue by Rudolph Besier and May Edginton, staged by Cecil Owen, with Dorothy Milburn, Helen Gilmore, Frank Harrington, Anne Bronaugh, et al. Associate Director, John Dugan.
  - Madame "X", November 17, 1924 (Box 1)
    The Alhambra Players present "Madame 'X'", A Drama in Three Acts and a Prologue, Adapted from the French of Alexandre Bisson by John Raphael, staged by Cecil Owen, with Anne Bronaugh, Kenneth Daigneau, Helen Gilmore et al. Associate Director, John Dugan.
  - One Day, December 15, 1924 (Box 1)
    The Alhambra Players present "One Day", A Sequel to "Three Weeks" by Elinor Glyn, in Four Acts, dramatized by Cecil Spooner, staged by Cecil Owen, with Ruth Mero, Harold Kennedy, Frank Harrington et al. Associate director, John Dugan.
  - Lazybones, January 5, 1925 (Box 1)
    The Alhambra Players present "Lazybones", A Chronicle of a Country Town by Owen Davis, staged by Cecil Owen, with Mabel Montgomery, Richard LaSalle, Ruth Mero, Harold Kennedy, Frank Harrington et al. Associate director, John Dugan.
  - Every Woman, January 19, 1925 (Box 1)
    The Alhambra Players present "Every Woman", A Modern Morality Play in Five Acts by Walter Browne, staged by Cecil Owen, with Richard LaSalle, Anne Bronaugh, Ruth Mero, Harold Kennedy, Fred House et al. Associate director, John Dugan.
  - A Play Without A Name, February 9, 1925 (Box 1)
    The Alhambra Players present "A Play Without A Name", A Comedy in Three Acts by Mabel Montgomery, staged by Cecil Owen, with Richard LaSalle, Mabel Montgomery, Frank Jamison, Ruth Mero, Anthony Stanford et al. Associate director, John Dugan.
  - No Other Girl [2 copies], February 16, 1925 (Box 1)
    The Alhambra Players present "No Other Girl", A Musical Comedy in Three Acts by Aaron Hoffman and Bert Kalmar, staged by Cecil Owen, with Richard LaSalle, Anne Bronaugh, Frank Jamison, Ruth Mero, Anthony Stanford et al. Associate director, John Dugan.
  - When Willie Comes Marching Home, April 22-24, [1950] (Box 1)
    John Ford's "When Willie Comes Marching Home" with Dan Dailey, Corinne Calvet, Colleen Townsend. Associate feature "Dakota Lil" starring George Montgomery, Rod Cameron, Marie Windsor.
  - N.T.G And His Radio Pals, October 19, [no year] (Box 1)
    N.T.G. And His Radio Pals, including John Irving Fisher and the entire Parody Club Revue, in addition to the regular big show. The following performers also appearing: Ted Lewis, Helen Dobbins, Consuela Owens, Mable Baade, Jean Wayne et al.
- American
  - Room Service, Jan. 16-21, [1949] (Box 1)
    The Marx Bros."Room Service", with Lucille Ball. "Carson City Raiders" with Allan Lane. Walter Wanger presents "Tap Roots", with Van Heflin, directed by George Marshall. "The Secret Land", with Robert Montgomery. Also,"Four Feathers" and "Marked Woman."
- Amphion
  - Faust, September 9, 1889 (Box 1)
    "Faust" under the Management of Edw. J. Abraham. Lewis Morrison as "Mephisto" in his Sublime Scenic and Dramatic Production of Goethe's Immortal play, with Mr. Russ Whytal, Mr. Porter J. White, Mr. Frederick Belasco, Miss Rosabel Morrison et al.
  - A Temperance Town, April 9, 1894 (Box 1)
    "A Temperance Town" by Chas H. Hoyt, also author of "A Milk White Flag", "A Trip to Chinatown", "A Texas Steer" etc., under the Management of Frank McKee, with Richard J. Dillon, Geo Richards, Eugene Canfield, et al.
  - The Chieftain, November 25, 1895 (Box 1)
    Francis Wilson and Company' American Presentation of "The Chieftain", A Comic Opera In Two Acts, composed by Sir Arthur Sullivan, written by F.C. Burnand, under the Management of Mr. A.H. Canby, with Francis Wilson, Mr. Rhys Thomas et al.
  - The Sunshine of Paradise Alley, November 1, 1897 (Box 1)
    Denman Thompson & George W. Ryer's Pictures of New York Life, entitled "The Sunshine of Paradise Alley" with John Walsh, John D. Griffin, et al.
  - The Wedding Day, March 14, 1898 (Box 1)
    The Lillian Russell, Della Fox, Jeff De Angelis Comic Opera Association. Mr. Frank Murray, Director. A New Comic Opera, "The Wedding Day", book by Stanislaus Stange, Music By Julian Edwards, with William Pruette, Lucille Saunders, et al.
- Amphion Theatre
  - Mr. Barnes of New York, January 18, [1888?] (Box 1)
  - The Carpet-Bagger, March 19, 1900 (Box 1)
    The American Character Comedian, Tim Murphy, Presenting the Political Romantic Comedy, In Four Acts "The Carpet-Bagger" by Opie Read and Frank S. Pixley, direction of T.E. Saunders, with Tim Murphy, John J. Shaw, J.R. Armstrong, et al.
  - Mrs. Jack, January 26, 1903 (Box 1)
    "Mrs. Jack", A Farcical Comedy, In Three Acts, by Grace Livingston Furniss, Management Henry B. Harris, with Miss Alice Fischer, Mrs. Thorndyke Boucicaut, Mr. Douglas F. Fairbanks, Miss Alice Leigh, et al.
  - The Vinegar Buyer, February 2, 1903 (Box 1)
    Ezra Kendall in "The Vinegar Buyer" A License for Laughter by Herbert Hall Winslow, Liebler & Co. Managers, with Eyra Kendall, Chas. Bowser, Ed. Chapman, et al.
  - A Chinese Honeymoon, April 27, 1903 (Box 1)
    "A Chinese Honeymoon", Messrs. Sam S. Shubert and Nixon & Zimmerman's Production of the English Musical Comedy, In Two Acts. Book and Lyrics by Mr. George Dance, Music by Mr. Howard Talbot. Staged by Mr. Gerard Coventry. R.A. Robert, director.
  - Variety Show: Novelties, Comedians, Music and Acting, September 11, 1905 (Box 1)
    Performance of a Medley Overture,"The Hippodrome" by Jean Schwartz. Burke's Musical Dogs, A Novelty. A Play in One Act "As A Man Sows" by Campbell McCulloch with Robert Hilliard et al. Steele, Doty & Coe, Comedy Musical Act.
- Arena
  - Keeper of the Flame, June 27-July 3, [1943] (Box 1)
    Movie program for "Keeper Of The Flame" with Spencer Tracy and Katharine Hepburn. Also "Death Valley Outlaws", "That Gang Of Mine", "I'm Still Alive", "Two Yanks in Trinidad", "Straight Shooter", "Moonlight Masquerade", "Wagon Train," etc. Dated via coverage in the Brooklyn Daily Eagle.
- Atlantic
  - Paradise For Two, March 7, 1927 (Box 1)
    Richard Dix in "Paradise For Two", with Betty Bronson and Andre Beranger. Bert Lytell in "The First Night", with Dorothy Devore, Harry Meyers et al. "Bertha, The Sewing Machine Girl", with Madge Bellamy and Allan Simpson.
  - London After Midnight, February 12, 1928 (Box 1)
    "London after Midnight", A Mystery Thriller, with Lon Chaney and Marceline Day. The Comedy "All for Nothing" with Clever Charlie Chase. Also playing, "Night Life", "The Lone Necker", "The College Widow" and "Find the King."
- Avoca Villa
  - Undertow, April 20, 1929 (Box 1)
    Movie program for Mary Nolan in "Undertow." Also Ken Maynard in "The Fighting Legion" and "Vengeance" with Jack Holt and Dorothy Revier. "Happy Days" and "White Cargo" also playing.
- Bedford Ave
  - Eight Bells, February 29, 1892 (Box 1)
    "8 Bells", Primrose and West's Comedy Company Presenting the Nautical Pantomimic Comedy in three acts, introducing the World-Famous Brothers Byrne, written and invented by John F. Byrne, with Percy Kingsley, C.F. Herbert, Geo W. Kerr et al.
  - The Westerner, April 11, 1892 (Box 1)
    A.M. DeLisser's Company, producing Edward E. Rose's Society Comedy, "The Westerner." Cast includes, Pauline Willard, Hattie Nefflen, Fannie Yantes, et al. Four Acts.
- Bensonhurst Hall
  - The Serious Family, June 16, 1893 (Box 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Presented by the Lyceum Dramatic Club.
- Bergen Beach Theatre
  - Rag-time Review, May 27, 1899 (Box 1)
    A Rag-Time Review, A Collection of Songs Popular the Past Season with Chorus Company, Miss May Powers, et al. and various novelty and comedy acts. The performance to conclude with a skit, "The Messiteers" with Bert Leslie, Andy Barr, et al.
  - A Spring Chicken, July 3, 1899 (Box 1)
    "A Spring Chicken", Edgar Selden's Three Act Music Farce. Overture-Medley: Louis Rinehart's Orchestra. Cast includes: Bert Leslie, Martie O'Neil, George Betts, Fred. Lucier, J.C. Flynn, Lou Paling, et al.
  - Natural Gas, August 7, 1899 (Box 1)
    "Natural Gas", Eddie Girard in Donnelly & Girard's Three Act Farce Comedy. Overture-Medley: Louis Rinehart's Orchestra. Cast includes: Edward Girard, Bert Leslie, George Betts, Andy Barr, Lou Paling, et al.
  - Town Topics, August 28, 1899 (Box 1)
    A.Q. Scammon's Three-Act Pantominic Comedy Farce, "Town Topics." With W.H. Mack, Will Dunalay, J.H. McMahon, Chas. E. Graham et al. Overture-Medley: Louis Rinehart's Orchestra. Specialties and Musical Numbers.
  - The Girl in Black, July 16, 1900 (Box 1)
    "The Girl In Black", A Rag-Time Pill, In Three Smokes, Book by Whatshisname, Music by Who'sthis, Overture-Medley: Louis Rinehart's Orchestra. Cast includes: Wm. Mitchell, Jno. J. Caine, Joseph Morris, Eleanor Falk, et al.
  - The Chimes of Normandy, August 6, 1900 (Box 1)
    The American Opera Company (Direction of Montegriffo and Allen) presents "The Chimes of Normandy", A Comic Opera in Three Acts, by Planquette, with Bell Travers, Edith Hutchins, et al. Eugene Rautenburg, Musical Director and Tom Hayes, Stage Manager.
- Bijou Theatre
  - The Two Orphans, April 25, [1897] (Box 1)
    D'Ennery's powerful Drama, "The Two Orphans." Annual Engagement of Kate Claxton and Chas. A. Stevenson, with Chas. A. Stevenson, Geo. Becks, Henry Stockbridge et al. Dated via coverage in the Brooklyn Eagle.
  - Othello, October 3, 1898 (Box 1)
    Managers Wagenhals & Kemper present "Othello", Shakespeare's Tragedy in Six Acts. Starring Louis James, Kathryn Kidder, Frederick Warde, with Mr. Frank Peters, Mr. Harry Langdon et al. Under the direction of H. C. Kennedy & Co.
  - A Female Drummer, January 2, [1899] (Box 1)
    "A Female Drummer", Chas. E. Blaney's Big Extravaganza Success. Music by Frank David, Lyrics by Chas. E. Blaney, with Miss Johnstone Bennett, Geo. Richards et al. Dated via coverage in the Brooklyn Eagle.
  - Casey's Wife, March 20, 1899 (Box 1)
    The Celtic-Hebraic Comedy, "Casey's Wife" by Robert J. Donnolly. A Farcical Pleasantry, about life in New York's East Side. Staged by Frank Tannehill, Jr., Direction of Fred Peel. Starring John C. Sparks, Claude Gillingwater, et al.
  - The Policy Players, October 30, [1899] (Box 1)
    Hurtig & Seamon present the World-Famed Comedians, William and Walker, In a New Musical Farce-Comedy, "The Policy Players." Music by Bert A. Williams, Book by Geo. W. Walker, Adapted for the stage by J.A. Shipp. Dated via coverage in the Brooklyn Eagle.
  - Why Smith Left Home, March 5, [1900] (Box 1)
    Broadhurst's Gleeful Plenitude, "Why Smith Left Home" by George H. Broadhurst, author of "What Happened to Jones" and "The Wrong Mr. Wright." With Maclyn Arbackle, Fred W. Peters, Dan Mason, et al. Dated via coverage in the Brooklyn Eagle.
  - Uncle Tom's Cabin, April 2, [1900] (Box 1)
    "Uncle Tom's Cabin" by Al. W. Martin, The only Legitimate Organization properly presenting this Ideal American Play, Al W. Martin, Sole Owner, with Will H. Stevens, Fred M. Tillish, Franklyn Whitman, et al. Staged under the direction of Will H. Stevens. Dated via coverage in the Brooklyn Eagle.
  - Our Cinderella, December 28, 1903 (Box 1)
    The Spooner Stock Company presents the Musical Comedy, "Our Cinderella" by William J. McKiernan, author of "The Gunner's Mate" etc. Staged and Produced by Edna May Spooner. Cast includes: Edna May Spooner, Cecil Spooner, Augustus Phillips, et al.
- Brighton Beach Baths
  - Daily Free Concerts, July 4, [no year] (Box 1)
    Events at Brighton Beach Baths. Daily free concerts. Harold Stern and his Orchestra, Willard Robison (presented by Rudy Vallee) and his Deep River Orchestra, Irving Aaronson and his Commanders. Swimming and other seasonal recreational activities.
- Brighton Beach Daily Music Programme
  - Sig. Luciano Conterno's Brighton Beach Band, June 12, 1882 (Box 1)
    Afternoon and Evening music program. Pieces include: "Billie Taylor", "Berlin as it Weeps and Laughs", "Hochzeitsreigen", "Concert Aria", "The Mayor", "Minuit", "Levy-Athen Polka", Flugschriften", "Wm. Tell", "Claude Duval", "Poet and Peasant", etc.
- Brighton Beach Hotel
  - Daily Music Concerts, August-September, 1910 (Box 1)
    Two Concerts Daily by Slafer and his Band of 100 Soloists and Vocalists.
  - Daily Music Concerts, July 24-29, [no year] (Box 1)
    Popular Concerts, twice daily, by Slafer and his Band. Selections from Offenbach, Von Tilzer, Verdi, Cohan, Sousa and others.
- Brighton Beach Music Hall
  - Fourth Week of the Season, 1890, July 19, 1890 (Box 1)
    The Metropolitan Orchestra. Conductor: Anton Seidl. Performing pieces by Weber, Dvorak, Strauss, Wagner, and others.
  - Second Week of the Season, 1891, July 4, 1891 (Box 1)
    Concerts every afternoon at 3:30 and every Evening at 8.00. Grand Matinees, Wagner and Symphonic Concerts and Novelties. The Metropolitan Orchestra. Conductor: Anton Seidl. Assistant Conductor: Victor Herbert. Concert Master: Clifford Schmidt.
  - Orpheus and Eurydice, 1899 (Box 1)
    Performances by Slafer's Brooklyn Marine Band (including "Orpheus and Eurydice"), Wiseman's Serenaders, The Great Van Aukens, Miss Louise Gunning, T. Wilmott Eckert and Miss Emma Berg, George Thatcher, Herbert's Wonderful Performing Dogs.
  - Poet and Peasant, July 10, 1899 (Box 1)
    Performances by Slafer's Brooklyn Marine Band (including "Poet and Peasant"), Eleanor Falk, Sadi Alfarabi, Carr and Jordan, Sisters Rappo, Florence Moore, Monroe & Jack. Music, comedy, dance and novelty acts. Programme changed weekly.
  - Jubel, September 4, 1899 (Box 1)